(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-08T21:49:52.039761",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
刮目せよ
Feast your eyes!
プロデューサー！！！
Producer!!!
次の生誕ライブ、なんにもやることないんですけど！！
For my upcoming birthday live, I've got nothing to do at all!!
毎年いろいろやってきたけど…
I've tried all sorts of things every year, but...
去年は、ミームやりすぎて、ミームキャラになっちゃったし、
last year I overdid the memes and became a meme character,
どうしようー
so what should I do?!
吾輩はどうやっていけば良いんだー！
What on earth should I do?!
勝手にTier表とか作っちゃいましたし…
[Producer: You even made that tier list without asking...]
それだ！
That's it!
ほら、吾輩、お姉さん大好きでしょ？
Look, I love older girls, right?
ホロライブのお姉さんを大集合させよう！
Let's gather all the older girls in Hololive!
お姉さんライブだ！！！
It'll be an "Older Girls Live"!
大丈夫だよ！当てはある！吾輩に任せとけ！
It's fine! I have some leads! Leave it to me!
それはちゃんとラプラスさんのライブとして成立するんですか？
[Producer: Will that really work as your own live concert, Laplus-san?]
そこは…なんかいい感じにやるんだよ！
I'll... figure that out and make it work somehow!
ていうか、吾輩のこと好きなファンならさ、やっぱり吾輩が好きなことしてるところ、楽しく見てくれるんじゃない？
I mean, if they're fans who love me, won't they just enjoy seeing me do what I love?!
限度があるんじゃないですか？
[Producer: Shouldn't there be a limit to that?]
とにかくやるって決めたらやるの！行くぞー！
Anyway, once I decide to do it, I'm doing it! Let's go!
ノエルさん！
Noel-san!
どうしたの？ラプちゃん？
What's up, Lap-chan?
実は、もうすぐ吾輩の生誕ライブがあるんですけど、よかったらノエルさんにも出てほしいなって…
The truth is, my birthday live is coming up soon, and I was wondering if you'd like to be in it...
えー！ラプちゃん誘ってくれるの！嬉しい！もちろんだよ！
Eh?! You're inviting me, Lap-chan?! I'm so happy! Of course!
よーし！団長、歌とダンス頑張っちゃおうかな！先輩として、かっこいいところ見せちゃうよー！
All right! Dancho is gonna give her all to singing and dancing! As your senpai, I'll show you my cool side!
あ、いや…歌は吾輩がやるんで…ね？ほら、これ持って！
Ah, no... I'll be doing the singing, so... okay? Here, hold this!
え、なに？どういうこと？これってうちわ？
Eh, what? What do you mean? Is this a fan?
さて、あとは何を歌うかですね…
[Producer: Now then, what will you sing...]
一曲目はね、きっとノエルさんも喜んでくれるはず！
For the first song, I'm sure Noel-san will love it!
え！？団長が？！
Eh?! Dancho will?!
去年からノエルさんの影響からか吾輩のファン層が広がって、こういう曲が喜んでもらえるかなー！って思って！
Since last year, maybe because of your influence, my fanbase has grown, so I thought this kind of song would make everyone happy!
えー！期待しちゃうけど…いいのおぉ！？
Ehh! My hopes are up now... is that really okay?!
良いですよー！一曲目盛り上がっていきましょおー！
It's totally fine! Let's hype it up for the first song!
キター！
[Noel: Here it comes!]
存外見掛け倒しな虚勢張ってるロマンス
A romance of unexpectedly all-talk posturing,
組み替えちゃって遺伝子
Recombining my genes,
オンリー・ロンリー・エマージェンシー
Only lonely emergency!
トゥケトゥケな電波に乗った感情論
An emotional argument riding jittery radio waves,
僕のアッピル見逃さないでよ
Don't miss out on my appeal!
人間なんてだれだって こういうのが好きなんだって
They say that all humans love stuff like this,
一人善がりオーガズミネイション 溢れて
A self-satisfied orgasm-nation overflowing,
ドヴァドヴァ 年季入りなあざとさ 「好き」の塗りたくり
Gushing out! Seasoned cuteness slathered with "I love you"s!
決めるぜ 僕のハッ 点！ ラヴ・バリ・ガル・マンダ！
I'll score my... eight points! Love-bari-gar-manda!
せーの！
Ready, set!
膨らんじゃった やっぱ お手加減 最高潮のをくれてやる
It's all swollen up! As expected, no holding back, I'll give you the ultimate climax!
「好き」って言葉で嬲って
Tormenting you with the word "love,"
迎え撃つから 君のアイデンティティティティーン
I'll meet you head-on with your identi-ti-ti-teen!
侮らないで 夢見がちボーイ
Don't underestimate me, you dreamy boy!
意外とありなんだって 気付いて
Realize that this is surprisingly great!
妄想フラストレイション
Delusional frustration,
毛頭暴走止まらない
Absolutely no stopping this rampage,
ギガンティック
Gigantic!
よそ見厳禁 見ててててね？
No looking away, keep your eyes on me, okay?
うわー！めっちゃ最高ー！
[Noel: Whoa! This is the absolute best!]
もっと輝いてくれー！
[Noel: Shine even brighter!]
可愛いぞー！
[Noel: You're so cute!]
3 2 1 で目覚めて 恋に落ちたりなんかして
3, 2, 1, wake up and maybe fall in love or something,
鷲掴んでシークレット あーなんだ やっぱり単純で
Grasp that secret! Ah, what do you know, it really is simple!
僕にとって僕が 揺るぎない絶対王政
To me, I am the unwavering absolute monarchy!
だからね 君だって僕が大好っきでしょ？
So that's why you love me so much, right?
見せてあげる聖域 僕だけの領域
I'll show you my sanctuary, my exclusive territory!
息遣いドキドキ 優しくして（バカ）
Heavy breathing, heart pounding, be gentle... (idiot)
山盛りな愛 want you アガっちゃって 恥じらっちゃって
Heaps of "I want you", getting hyped up, getting embarrassed,
狂っちゃえばイージーモード
Once you go crazy, it's easy mode!
油断大敵マジモード
Stay on guard, it's serious mode!
ワンタッチでリッチなビッチ
With one touch, a rich bitch
とろとろに溶かして 愛 need you
melts gooey and soft, "I need you"!
誤算過ぎた僕のエラートラップ
A total miscalculation, my error trap!
ペロペロ舐めないで
Don't lick it all over,
ここは限界突破ラヴゲーム
here's our limit-breaking love game!
加速しちゃって やっぱ お手加減 最高超のを魅せてやれ
Accelerating! As expected, no holding back, show off the highest super-level!
駆け引き上手な僕がルール
Master of tactics, I make the rules!
狙い撃ち 君をプラマイプラスで
Aiming and shooting you with plus-minus-plus,
引き返せない 二人だけの秘密
There's no turning back, a secret just between the two of us!
意外とありかもなんて 気付いた？
Realized that maybe it's surprisingly okay?
罪作りラヴポーション
Sinful love potion!
一切合切とめどない
Absolutely unstoppable,
ギガンティック
Gigantic!
目移りなんて許さないね？
Looking away won't be forgiven, okay?
おちんちんはギガンティックO.T.Nの略称である
"Ochinchin" is the abbreviation for Gigantic O.T.N.
主にXXやXYなどの組み合わせで扱われており、男女兼用である
It's primarily handled in combinations like XX and XY, and is unisex.
最近では…あ！間違えた！
Recently... Ah! I messed up!
頑張れー！
[Noel: You can do it!]
えーと、携帯のO.T.Nという画期的なものが開発され…
Um, an innovative portable O.T.N was developed...
…タッチが楽しめたり、何だったっけ…
...so you could enjoy the touch, and what was it again...
…全く別の話になっちゃった！違う違う！もう以上だ！全部忘れてきたー！
...I started talking about something completely different! No, no! That's enough! I forgot everything!
膨らんじゃった やっぱ お手加減 最高潮のをくれてやる
It's all swollen up! As expected, no holding back, I'll give you the ultimate climax!
「好き」って言葉で嬲って
Tormenting you with the word "love,"
迎え撃つから 君のアイデンティティティティーン
I'll meet you head-on with your identi-ti-ti-teen!
侮らないで 夢見がちボーイ
Don't underestimate me, you dreamy boy!
踏み乱れ撃ち
Chaotic rapid fire
ラプくんの時代が来た！
Lap-kun's era has come!
ショタかわちいよ、ラプくん！かわちいよ！
Shotas are so cute, Lap-kun! So cute!
最後まで輝いて！
Keep shining until the very end!
さすがに先輩をファン扱いするのはどうかと思いますよ？
I don't think you should really treat your senior like a fan, though?
いや、ノエルさんはファンでしょ！
No way, Noel-san is definitely a fan!
ファンっていうか、ママになろうとしてる人…？
Or rather than a fan, someone trying to become my mama...?
とにかく、めっちゃ盛り上がってましたやん！
Anyway, she was super hyped up, wasn't she!
てかてか、お姉さんといえばホロライブって学校みたいじゃない？
Speaking of big sisters, isn't Hololive kind of like a school?
学校？
A school?
学校のみんなのアイドル…そらさん
The school's beloved idol... Sora-san.
隣のクラスの留学生…キアラさん
The exchange student in the class next door... Kiara-san.
凛とした清楚な先輩…AZKiさん
The dignified, refined senior... AZKi-san.
部活の先輩お姉さま…ネリッサ
The cool big sister senior in the club... Nerissa.
クールビューティーな先生…クロニー
The cool beauty teacher... Kronii.
そして、同じクラスにいる、うるさい幼馴染の同級生…いろは
And my noisy childhood friend and classmate in the same room... Iroha.
そうだ！これをライブでやれば、盛り上がること間違いなし！
That's it! If I do this at a live concert, it'll definitely hype everyone up!
そうと決まれば早速突撃だー！
Now that that's settled, let's charge right in—!
次から次へとすごい行動力だ…
Her drive, jumping from one thing to the next, is incredible...
いろはー！
Iroha—!
うん？なんでござるか！？
Hm? What is it de gozaru?!
ライブでやりたい曲あるんだけど、見ててくんない？
There's a song I want to do at the live, won't you watch me?
？？？見る？？？どういうことでござる？
??? Watch??? What do you mean by that, de gozaru?
そう！見るだけ！やっぱり幼馴染と言えばいつでも見守ってくれる存在だからね！
Yeah! Just watch! After all, childhood friends are always there watching over you!
ただそこにいるだけで良い、そばにいてくれるだけ、その温かさが沁みるんだ
Just being there is enough, just being by my side, that warmth really touches me.
え…なんか気持ちわるいでござる…
Uh... that's kind of creepy, de gozaru...
いいからいいから！さ！行くぞー！
It's fine, it's fine! Come on, let's go—!
え？ な、これ...
Eh? Wh-what is this...?
な、な、な、なこれ？ な、な、な、な、なこれー！？
Wh-wh-what is this? Wh-wh-what is this—?!
え？ 何？
Eh? What?
え、何？ え、何？ え？
Eh, what? Eh, what? Eh?
ラプラスちゃん？
Laplus-chan?
お、おお？ お？ え？ え？ え？
Oh, oh? Oh? Eh? Eh? Eh?
隣のクラスで最近ちょっと気になってるあの娘
That girl in the class next door I've been eyeing recently
声が！
Her voice?!
すました顔して不意に見せたときめきスマイル
Acting cool, she suddenly flashed a heart-throbbing smile
ときめきスマイル？
Heart-throbbing smile?!
いやいやいやいや別に好きとかそんなんじゃないよ
No, no, no, no, it's not like I actually like her or anything
ただちょっと ちょっと ちょっと 目の保養にしてるだけだってば！
I'm just, just, just using her as eye candy, that's all!
目の保養！？
Eye candy?!
頭ん中結構メロメロなんだって
Inside my head, I'm completely head over heels
勉強もう全然頭に入ってこなくても
Even if studying won't get through my head at all
ヤバイ！ 君に夢中さ
Oh no! I'm crazy about you
ヤバイ？
Oh no?
ほらね吐いて吐いて
Come on, spit it out, spit it out
吐いて！？
Spit it out?!
こんな2次元の狭間でこえてけ境界線
In the threshold of 2D, cross over the boundary line
君が直接生でとことん逝ってきまーす！
You go directly in the flesh, all the way to heaven!
怖ーいって！
That's scary!
あーやべえ やべえ
Ah, this is bad, so bad
これ何？何これ？ソロライブ？何これ？
What is this? What is this? A solo live? What is this?
何ってライブだよ！
What do you mean, it's a live concert!
何のライブ！？何のライブ！？
A live concert of what?! Of what?!
どこ見てんだよ！
Where are you looking?!
黙ってろっつってんだろ！
I told you to shut up!
はい、イントロ
Alright, into the intro!
ピッと伸ばす背筋 (ピピッ)
Straighten up your spine (Beep beep)
前進のテクテクで 脳内微震
Marching forward step by step, brain trembles
大・大・挫折に な・な・な・泣き落としちゃう
Massive, massive setbacks, cr-cr-cry it all out
君の 君の 君の 君の 君の 君の 君の
Your, your, your, your, your, your, your
フ○ッキン！
Fxxkin'!
見して 見して もっと 見して 見して ちゃんと
Show me, show me, show me more, show me properly
見して 見して 見て ABCD 4つ
Show me, show me, look, ABCD, the 4 of them
立って 我慢 ちょっと 我慢 やっぱ 我慢 できない
Stand and endure, hold back a bit, nope, can't hold back
した・した・思春期 痛そう こらこらもう
Puberty in full swing, looks painful, hey, hey now
あ、返すとダメか？ え？
Ah, I shouldn't talk back? Eh?
3学年の美人で大人で博識優しい先輩
The 3rd-year beautiful, mature, knowledgeable, kind senpai
そんなに顔近づけられたらもうドキドキ止まんなくて
Getting your face so close makes my heart race nonstop
あっ！…風で制服の隙間チラ見して
Ah!... Glancing at the gap in her uniform from the wind
スカート5cm折ったら最高！見えちゃった最高！
Folding the skirt 5cm is the best! I caught a glimpse, the best!
生きてる？ 生きてるって！ 何言ってんのよ！
Are you alive? You're alive! What are you saying?!
昼休み AKB ええ加減にせえよ！
Lunch break, AKB, cut it out already!
自分でやらなきゃだめ？
Do I have to do it myself?
肉 豚肉の生姜焼き
Meat, ginger fried pork
先輩に描く放物線 上にとった下にトッ！
Tracing a parabola to Senpai, took it above, then down!
スナイパー ルージュで仕留めたスコープ
Sniper, scope locked on with rouge
母校の生徒も止められない 本能のオレの
Even the alma mater students can't stop my primal instinct's
し・し・せっく…す！
S-S-Sex...!
うっ！
Ugh!
どっちを選ぶの？
Which one will you choose?
うっ？ ごめんなさい...
Uh? I'm sorry...
先輩！ イマジナリーお姉さんと交信してる！
Senpai! She's communicating with an imaginary big sister!
おーい！
Hey!
どっちも！
Both of them!
しょうがねえだろ！
Can't be helped, right?!
すみませんでしたーー！
I'm so sorryーー!
ピッと伸ばす背筋 (ピピッ)
Straighten up your spine (Beep beep)
前進のテクテクで 脳内微震
Marching forward step by step, brain trembles
死ぬ手前で 駄目・駄目・駄目・駄目 クラッ どうしちゃう
On the verge of dying, no, no, no, no, dizzy, what to do
俺の 俺の 俺の 俺の 俺の 俺の
My, my, my, my, my, my
フ○ッキン！
Fxxkin'!
こっち こっち もっと こっち こっち ちゃんと
Here, here, more over here, here, properly
ちゃんと見ろって事？
You mean look properly?
こっち こっち 見て ABCD 4つ
Look here, look here, ABCD, the 4 of them
立って 引いて ちょっと 引いて やっぱ 危険 ピーピー
Stand and back off, step back a bit, danger after all, beep beep
欲したしたい年頃で そろそろほらもう
At the age of craving it, come on, it's about time
ちょっとだけ (ねぇ) ちょっとだけ (見せて)
Just a little (Hey) Just a little (Show me)
ちょっとだけ (ほら)
Just a little (Come on)
ちょっと男子！
Hey, you boys!
ちょっとだけ (ねぇ) ちょっとだけ (見せて)
Just a little (Hey) Just a little (Show me)
ちょっとだけ 後悔してる？
Are you regretting it just a little?
エロ！
Pervert!
1, 2
え？ 何？ 何何？ 着席？ 着席っす？
Eh? What? What is it? Sit down? We sit down?
礼、礼！ 合わせろ合わせろ！
Bow, bow! Match me, match me!
3, 4
そうそうそう、いいよいいよ、おーおーおー
Yeah, yeah, yeah, nice, nice, oh, oh, oh
5, 6
わかんねえ、早えって！
I don't know, you're too fast!
7, 8
あっ！
Ah!
手を合わせてください
Put your hands together, please.
はい
Yes.
みんな元気に、いただきます！
Everyone, full of energy: Itadakimasu!
ワン、ツー
One, two,
さよなら
goodbye!
え、三角...四角...待って待って！
Wait, triangle... square... Wait, wait!
先生、みなさん、おちんぽこ〜！
Teacher, everyone, ochinpoko~!
元気すぎるだろ
You're way too hyper!
ピンセトバズマすりぃ 前進前進
Pinset Bazuma Surii, forward, forward,
乗ってけペケペケ波しぶき
ride the peke-peke spray of the waves!
時代 大盛り上がり
The era is booming,
なかなかどうして
quite indeed,
誰に話しかけてるの？ 怖い！
Who are you talking to? Scary!
どうしちゃう
what should I do?
君の 君の 君の 君の
Falling in love with you, you, you, you,
FUCK YOU WITH ME!
見して 見して ちょ、見して 見して
Show me, show me, wait, show me, show me,
見して 見して 見て ABCDEF
show me, show me, look at ABCDEF!
怒られるよ！ やめな、やめな、ちょっと！
You'll get scolded! Stop it, stop it, hey!
我慢 やっぱ我慢できない
Patience, I can't hold it back after all!
舌 舌 舌 思春期で
Tongue, tongue, tongue, in puberty,
外 この 子供！
outside, this kid!
F, U, C, K, U, P, H, Y, S, I, C...
急に乗った割には大丈夫そう？
For jumping into it so suddenly, you seem fine?
あ、最後までね、ごちそうさまでした！
Ah, all the way to the end, thanks for the feast!
急に...ごちそうさまでした？
Suddenly... "thanks for the feast"?
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
マジでいろはすビジネスでよかった〜
I'm so glad Irohasu is just business~
ギムギム、バイバーイ
Gimu gimu, bye-bye!
だね、帰るね
Yeah, heading home now.
[プロデューサー: どうしたんですか？]
[Producer: What's the matter?]
ねえねえ！プロデューサーの好みってどんな人なん？
Hey, hey! What kind of person is your type, Producer?
[プロデューサー: え～…]
[Producer: Well...]
ほら、ホロライブっていんな人いるじゃん？
I mean, Hololive has all kinds of people, right?
しゅびしゅわ～、すーの充電たりてる～？ 水宮枢だよー！
Shubishuwa~ Is Su's charge topped up~? It's Su Mizumiya!
わっしょーい！ホロライブの清楚担当！みんなのアイドル〜夏色〜まつりでーす！
Wasshoi! In charge of Hololive's purity! Everyone's idol, Matsuri Natsuiro here!
みなさん、待ったかね～ホロライブ6期生、holoXの女幹部 鷹嶺ルイと申します～！
Everyone, did you wait for me? Hololive 6th Gen, holoX's executive, Lui Takane at your service!
はーい、みなさま～、こんらみ～！ホロライブ5期生の顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！
Hi everyone, Kon-Lamy~! Hololive 5th Gen's liver of the group, Lamy Yukihana here!
Good evening! My Cute students. ちょこーんと
Good evening! My cute students. Chokoon!
ホロライブ2期生、悪魔のバーチャル保健医 癒月ちょこでーす！ちょこーん！
Hololive 2nd Gen's devilish virtual school nurse, Choco Yuzuki here! Chokoon!
Ahoy! ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンですぅー！
Ahoy! Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Marine Houshou here~!
[プロデューサー: みなさんとても魅力的ですよ？]
[Producer: Everyone is very charming, you know?]
いやいや、そういうんじゃないでしょ
No, no, that's not what I mean.
[プロデューサー: いやぁー仕事ですからね。ホロライブの方で…とかはないですよ]
[Producer: Well, it's work after all. I wouldn't do anything like that with Hololive members.]
ふーん
Hmm...
[プロデューサー: ただ、最近の趣味といえば…]
[Producer: Though, if we're talking about recent hobbies...]
[プロデューサー: ******]
[Producer: * * * * * *]
え… いやぁ… それは… 流石に… すごい趣味してるな…
Huh... Well... that's... certainly... quite a taste you have...
[プロデューサー: この人に言われたくないな…]
[Producer: I don't want to hear that from you...]
あ！こんな時間じゃん！吾輩ちょっとこの後用事あるんで…じゃ！
Ah! Look at the time! I've got something to take care of after this, so... see ya!
[横画面で開始します]
[Starting in landscape mode]
初めて呼んじゃったぜ
I ordered one for the first time.
やべー
Man...
高かったー
That was expensive~
でも、まあ可愛かったから、いっか
But well, she was cute, so whatever.
ジャケット、どっか
Where's the jacket...
クリーニングし
sent to dry cleaning...
着ちゃった
Oh, I'm wearing it.
はっ
Ah.
え？
Huh?
よいしょ
Hup...
え？
Huh?
ちょっ…えっ
Wait... huh?
これですか？
Is this it?
初心者みたいの来ちゃったんですけど…
A beginner showed up, though...
え？
Eh?
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ NO THANK YOU!
Change, change, change, NO THANK YOU!
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ で NO THANK YOU!
Change, change, change, I said NO THANK YOU!
それじゃちょっと息抜きでもしましょうかって感じで
Feeling like taking a little breather,
チラシの番号に TEL
I called the number on the flyer.
たまたまドンピシャで気に入った子がいたんで
By chance, there was a girl who was totally my type,
胸の大きい方をチョイス
so I chose the one with bigger breasts.
「髪型ショートで攻めるのが得意な子」
"A girl with short hair who likes to take charge."
「今からそちらへお送りいたしますぅ」
"We will send her right over to you~"
ドアを開けたら 別れた彼女
When I opened the door, it was my ex-girlfriend.
おいおい こいつは一体全体 何の冗談だ
Hey, hey, what on earth kind of joke is this?!
デリヘル呼んだら君が来た
I ordered a delivery health girl and you showed up.
虚ろな目をして立っていたんだ
You stood there with hollow eyes.
あなたの好みのタイプになって 帰ってきましたって
Saying, "I came back after becoming your preferred type."
ロミジュリ張りの悲劇に酔い 傷つき抉り研ぎ澄ますガード
Intoxicated by a tragedy like Romeo and Juliet, gouging open wounds and sharpening our guard,
街頭を見渡して 大声で さぁ
looking over the street, at the top of my lungs, come on!
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ NO THANK YOU!
Change, change, change, NO THANK YOU!
朝の...
The morning...
さあ 今日はご機嫌如何ですか お嬢
Now, how are you feeling today, young lady?
なかなかの塩梅で
In pretty good shape.
隣の部屋 喘ぐのは女子大生 ほら今も
Next door, a college girl is moaning, look, even now
BPM 約120で
at a BPM of around 120.
妄想に surrender デズライ踏んだから
Surrendering to delusions, since I crossed the death line,
たまにはフリー指定 小柄な子にしようか
maybe for once I'll pick a free designation, a petite girl?
ドアを開けたら 新人 案の定
When I opened the door, a newcomer, just as expected.
おいおい どんな魔法を使ったってんだよ
Hey, hey, what kind of magic did you use?!
ホテヘル行ったら君がいた 虚ろな目をして立ってたんだ
When I went for delivery health, you were there, standing with vacant eyes.
「貴方の好みのタイプは全部わかっているのよ」って
Saying, "I know all about your favorite type."
制服 人妻 ナース OL 行く店の日並み 全部登場
Uniform, housewife, nurse, OL—every shop I visit, you appear in all!
オプションは頼まない
I won't order any options,
延長もしない
nor will I extend the time!
行くぞー！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set!
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ ノーサンキュー！
Change, change, change, no thank you!
真夜中起きたら君がいた 虚ろな目をして立ってたんだ
When I woke in the middle of the night, you were there, standing with vacant eyes.
「貴方の好みのタイプになって帰ってきました」って
Saying, "I came back transformed into your exact type."
思い出したくもない笑顔が トラウマとなって住み着いた
A smile I don't even want to remember became trauma and moved right in.
哀愁を見合わして 絶賛 逃亡中
Facing sorrow, I'm fully on the run,
さあ せーの！
now, ready, set!
チェンジ チェンジ チェンジ ノーサンキュー！
Change, change, change, no thank you!
まじか...
Seriously...?
ま、次だな...
Well, on to the next one...
ふぅ...
Phew...
いや、いいんだよ、プロデューサーの好みとか！
No, it doesn't matter what your personal preference is, Producer!
聞いたのは、そっちです
[Producer: You're the one who asked.]
ちょっとちょっと、ケンカしてどうしたの！
Hold on, hold on, what are you two fighting about?!
あっ、こよちゃーん！！！ 聞いてよー！プロデューサーのやつが〜！！！
Ah, Koyo-chan!!! Listen to this! This Producer guy is, like...!!!
うんうん
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
それで、あいつがさ〜〜〜！！
And then he was like...!!
そうだね〜ラプちゃん辛かったね〜
I hear ya~ You had a rough time, Lapu-chan~
はぁ、ここまでいろんなホロメンと絡んできたけど、やっぱりこよちゃんが一番だよ！！
Haa... I've hung out with so many Holo members up until now, but Koyo-chan, you really are the best!!
そうだ！今度の吾輩の生誕ライブ一緒に出ようよ！こよちゃんと吾輩にぴったりな曲があるんだ！
I know! Join me for my upcoming Birthday Live! I've got the perfect song for the two of us!
ライブの出演ね！スケジュール…確認しておくね〜！
Performing at your live, huh! Let me... check my schedule~!
ありがとー！じゃあまたステージで！！
Thank you! See you on stage, then!!
(俺、このライブが終わったら…君と…)
(Once this live concert is over... I'll tell you...)
横画面で開始します
[Starting in landscape mode]
時計の針が
As the hands of the clock
10から12に回るまで
turn from ten to twelve,
頭の中
inside my head,
染められていく Pink Pink Light
it gets completely dyed in pink, pink light.
すれ違いあたり ふと目が交じわるだけで
Just brushing past and having our eyes meet for a moment
宙に浮いてる気分になる
makes me feel like I'm floating in midair.
でもそんなこと 君は知らないし
But you don't have a clue about any of that, do you?
ねえ！
Hey!
手を繋ぎたい キスをしたい 君と半径10m以内
I want to hold hands, I want to kiss, within a 10-meter radius of you,
でも叶わない だから妄想で今日もジャグリング
but it won't come true, so today too I'm juggling through delusions!
君のことに一喜一憂
Riding an emotional rollercoaster over everything about you,
だって好きだから
because I love you so much!
こっち向いて 待って待って
Look this way! Wait, wait,
やっぱ向いて 独り占めしたいの
look at me after all! I want you all to myself.
こっち向いて わがままな歌って
Look this way! Even if it's a selfish song,
分かってるけど だってだってだって
I know it is, but still, but still, but still...
目があって 照れ隠しで
Our eyes meet, and hiding my embarrassment,
意地悪してるの 気づいて
please notice that I'm just acting mean.
君のせいで ドキドキ送信 どうしてくれる
Because of you, my heart is pounding and sending signals—what are you gonna do about it?
Yeah!
Sunday Monday チュウして ギュウして 毎日
Sunday, Monday, kiss me, hug me every day!
クリンチ 見抜いて 激急ピッチ
Clinch, see through it at breakneck speed!
気抜けさキューティ 一途にぼっち
Careless cutie, single-mindedly all alone,
あっち そっち こっち向いて どっち
Over there, that way, look over here, which way?
はやまる鼓動のBPM 日に日に好きになる S M L
My racing heartbeat's BPM, liking you more day by day, S M L!
わかってよなんて自分勝手
Wanting you to understand is so selfish of me,
やっぱり きっぱり とびっきりのLuv
But after all, clearly, it's the ultimate Luv!
新鮮なこの思い トゥインクル
These fresh feelings, twinkle!
君に伝えたい ぴんこす
I want to tell you, pinkos!
脳内選挙 レベルは最強
Elections in my brain, level is invincible,
手付かず勉強 許してご愛嬌
Haven't touched my studies, forgive my charm!
胸のときめきも絶頂
The throbbing in my chest is at its peak!
待ちに待った今日 君とランデブー
The long-awaited today, a rendezvous with you!
ご一緒なんて 妄想ですます 憂いのShow
Being together is just a fantasy in this sorrowful show!
こっち向いて
Look this way,
待って 待って
Wait, wait!
やっぱ向いて
Actually, do look!
恥ずかしいだけど こっち向いて
It's embarrassing, but look this way!
君の目に映った 自分の
Reflected in your eyes,
顔が赤い気がして
I feel like my face is turning red...
目が合った
Our eyes met,
手が触れた
Our hands touched,
それだけで
Just with that,
一大事なんだもん
It's a huge deal!
ねぇだって
Hey, because...
君のことが
It's about you...
この先が どうしてなの言えないの
Why can't I say what comes next?
まぶたの裏 思い浮かべて
Behind my eyelids, picturing your face,
好きだよ 好きなの ねぇ
I love you, I really do, hey...
思うだけで幸せなのは
Just thinking of you makes me happy,
本当はちょっと切ない
But truth is, it's a little bittersweet.
口を出る強がり 見栄切って寂しがり
Bluffing with my words, showing off yet feeling lonely,
実はもう限界
Truth is, my limits
超えてんの だけど
Have already been passed, but...
言えるはずない
I could never say it,
言えるわけない
There's no way I can say it!
臆病なハートに
Give my cowardly heart
後押しして Want me
A little push, want me!
こっち向いて
Look this way,
待って 待って
Wait, wait!
やっぱ向いて
Actually, do look!
独り占めしたいの
I want to have you all to myself!
こっち向いて
Look this way,
わがままだって
I know it's selfish,
わかってるけど
But even so...
だって だって だって だって
Because, because, because, because...
目が合って
Our eyes meet,
高鳴って
My heart races,
赤くなって
Blushing red,
百面相してるの
Making all kinds of funny faces!
今日だって
Even today,
君のせいで
All because of you,
ドキドキ忙しい
My pounding heart is kept busy!
神様 お願い
Dear God, please,
ちょっとでいいから
Just a little bit is fine,
勇気をください
Please give me courage!
カジキマグロ
Swordfish!
ドン！
Boom!
プロデューサーぁぁぁ！！！
Producer-aaaaaah!!!
どうしたんですか？
What happened?
こよちゃんにフラれたぁ〜
Koyo-chan dumped meee~!
フラれるとかあるんですね？
Getting dumped is actually a thing for you?
ちくしょう！！！こうなったら！！！
Dammit!!! If it's come to this...!!!
嫌な予感がする
I have a bad feeling about this.
誰でもいいから付き合いたーい！！
I just want to date anyone at all!!
そうなったらもう終わりですよ
If it's come to that, you're already finished.
うるさい！
Shut up!
吾輩は…彼女作って幸せになるんだー！！！！！
I'm gonna... get a girlfriend and be happy!!!!!
やるぞ…
Let's do this...
緊張するな…
I'm so nervous...
やったるぞ…
I'm gonna give it my all...
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I just wanna date anyone!
もう誰でもいいから
Seriously, anyone will do!
男の前では喋れても
Even if I can talk in front of guys,
女の前では喋れない
I can't speak in front of girls.
トラウマだらけの僕の過去
My trauma-filled past
涙なしでは語れない
Can't be told without tears.
どうして彼女が出来ないの
Why can't I get a girlfriend?
「僕は素敵」だと君は言う
You tell me, "You're wonderful."
「それなら僕と付き合ってよ」
"Then go out with me!"
その苦笑いは意味深に
That strained smile of yours is so telling...
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I just wanna date anyone!
もう誰でもいいから
Seriously, anyone will do!
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I just wanna date anyone!
もう誰でもいいから
Seriously, anyone will do!
誰でもいいから付き合いたい
I just wanna date anyone!
もう誰でもいいから
Seriously, anyone will do!
なんで…
Why...?
なんでだよぉ〜〜
Why does it have to be like this~~?!
全員からフラれたぁぁぁ〜〜〜！！！
Every single one of them dumped meee~~~!!!
うーん、このライブ、大丈夫かな
Hmm, is this live concert going to be okay?
くそ、もうこうなったら！
Dammit, if it's come to this!
えぇ！？なんですかそれ！
Huh!? What is that?!
この封印を…解放してやるぅ！！！
I will... unseal this power...!!!
俺の聖植を…爆裂させてやるぅ！！！ウォーーーーー！！！
I'll make my holy horns explode...!!! Waaaaahhh---!!!
お、おしまいだこのライブは… もはやライブなのかも怪しい所…
Th-this concert is doomed... At this point, I doubt if this is even a concert...
横画面で開始します
Please start in landscape mode
聖槍爆裂ボーイ
作詞・作曲：れるりり＆もじゃ
Sacred Spear Explosion Boy
Lyrics & Music: rerulili & moja
なんていうか大きな声で言うことではないかもしれませんが
How should I put this? It might not be something to say out loud, but...
男女に備わったあれとそれ
what men and women are equipped with: this and that,
正乱晴天土乱とのいわばあれとそれ
the so-called this and that of order and chaos.
そんなこんなで起こるhappening
With this and that, things happen,
あっという間に僕のending
and in the blink of an eye, it's my ending.
誤って悩んで困ってしまって
Making mistakes, worrying, getting into trouble,
どうしよってなにもできない無情
wondering what to do, utterly helpless, how merciless.
0.02mmの壁がすげーもどかしくなって
The 0.02mm barrier becomes so terribly frustrating,
真っ赤な my sunshine
my bright red sunshine.
すぐに入れたくなるのは君のせい
Wanting to put it right in is all your fault.
「いいじゃーん」とかそんな気分で迎えた君と僕そんなヘブンで
"Why not?" In that mood, you and I met in that heaven,
しまったって思っても もう遅い
and even if we think "crap," it's already too late.
アップサイド・インサイドアウト
Upside inside out,
I defend you 甘噛み you の髪
I defend you, nibbling softly on your hair.
一切合切愛で返事
Answering everything and anything with love.
I'm coming. You're coming.
待ってこれって僕のせい？
Wait, is this my fault?
「生でいいよ」って言った君のせい？
Or your fault for saying "raw is fine"?
そして5分で終わるテストって
And a test that finishes in five minutes...
信憑性欠けるもんだって
lacks credibility, you know!
しっかり刻まれた十字架に
Nailed to the clearly engraved cross,
張り付けられた僕は切り捨てに
I'm cast aside,
なったって無理ってわかっているって
knowing it's useless even if that happens,
どうしよってなにもできない
wondering what to do, utterly powerless.
0.02mmの壁がすげー悩ましくなって
The 0.02mm barrier becomes so terribly tormenting,
真っ青な my sunshine
my deep blue sunshine.
すぐに入れたくなるのは僕のせい
Wanting to put it right in is my fault.
大丈夫とかそんな気分で甲斐性もないこんな身分で
"It'll be fine," in that mood, completely unreliable,
泣いたって怒ったって 後の祭り
crying or getting angry won't change a thing now.
マキシマムインサートなう
Maximum insert now.
Are you ready? 愛撫ハニー 指噛み
Are you ready? Caressing honey, biting fingers.
聖槍爆裂ボーイ
Sacred spear explosion boy.
愛が feeling. I have honey. You be coming.
Love is feeling. I have honey. You be coming.
遠い夏の思い出
Memories of a distant summer,
君の長い髪が揺れる
your long hair swaying...
嗚呼…
Ah...
待ってこれって僕のせい？
Wait, is this my fault?
「中に出して」って言った君のせい？
Or your fault for saying "finish inside"?
そして5分で終わるテストって
And a test that finishes in five minutes...
絶対的二元論だって
is an absolute binary matter!
十月十日ばかりの運命を
Ruling over a destiny
支配している僕は神様に
of mere forty weeks, can I
なれないって無理ってわかっていて
never become a god? Knowing it's impossible,
結局なにも解決してない
in the end nothing is solved at all.
0.02mmの壁がすげーもどかしくなって
The 0.02mm barrier becomes so terribly frustrating,
真っ白な my sunshine
my pure white sunshine.
すぐに入れたくなるのは君のせい
Wanting to put it right in is all your fault.
「いいじゃーん」とかそんな気分で迎えた君と僕そんなヘブンで
"Why not?" In that mood, you and I met in that heaven,
しまったって思っても もう遅い
and even if we think "crap," it's already too late.
アップサイド・インサイドアウト
Upside inside out,
I defend you 甘噛み you の髪
I defend you, nibbling softly on your hair.
一切合切愛で返事
Answering everything and anything with love.
I'm coming. You're coming.
マキシマムインサートなう
Maximum insert now.
Are you ready? 愛撫ハニー 指噛み
Are you ready? Caressing honey, biting fingers.
聖槍爆裂ボーイ
Sacred spear explosion boy.
愛が feeling. I have honey. You be coming.
Love is feeling. I have honey. You be coming.
嗚呼…
Ah...
いやあ、まさか、聖槍でライブ会場壊しちゃうなんて
Man, who would've thought you'd destroy the live venue with a sacred spear...
つい…力を解放してしまった…
I accidentally... unleashed my power...
それにしても、みんなひどくない？吾輩を振るなんて…
Even so, isn't everyone so cruel? Dumping me like that...
もうやってらんないよ～
I can't take this anymore~!
（ここはあの手を使うしかない）
(I have no choice but to use that trick.)
ラプラスさん、実は、あの方に来ていただいてます！
Laplus-san, actually, we invited that person over!
あの方？
That person?
ラプくん？どうしたのー？
Lap-kun? What's wrong~?
うわっ！？あ、あ、あじゅ姉！？まさか、吾輩のために来てくれたの？？？？
Whoa!? A-A-Aju-nee!? Did you seriously come here just for me????
当然だよー！だって今日は、ラプくんの誕生日でしょー？
Of course! Because today is Lap-kun's birthday, right?
あ、やばい、吾輩今日が命日かもしれん…
Ah, oh no, today might be the day I die of happiness...
お誕生日おめでとー！プレゼントは何がいいのかな～？
Happy birthday~! What would you like for a present~?
え！プレゼントってなんでももらえるの？！
Eh! Can I get anything as a present?!
あじゅがあげられるものなら何でも大丈夫だゾ☆
As long as it's something Aju can give, anything is fine☆
えー！！えええ！じゃあ――
Eeh!! Whaaat! Then—
え？今なんて言ったの？変な音で聞こえなかった！
Eh? What did you just say? I couldn't hear over that weird sound!
あれ？
Huh?
なんだこれー！届かないぞ吾輩の願いが！
What is this?! My wish isn't reaching her!
あぶない…危うく配信できないところだった…
That was close... We almost couldn't stream this...
邪魔するなプロデューサー――！！！！！
Don't get in my way, Producer—!!!!!
なんか色々大変そうだから…今日はこの辺で帰るね！今日は本当におめでと～！ラプくん、また遊ぼうね～
Seems like you've got a lot going on... I'll head home for today! Happy birthday once again! Lap-kun, let's hang out again~
帰るね！
I'm heading home now!
今日は本当におめでと〜！
Happy birthday today!
ラプくん、また遊ぼうね〜
Lap-kun, let's hang out again~
あ、あじゅねぇ！
Ah, Ajune!
あじゅねぇぇぇぇぇ！！！！
Ajune-eeeeee!!!!
[プロデューサー] え、はい、はい、分かりました！
[Producer: "Yes, right, understood!"]
[プロデューサー] ラプラスさん！新曲オーディションですって！
[Producer: "Laplus-san! It's a new song audition!"]
どゆこと！？
What do you mean?!
[プロデューサー] 新曲だけのオーディション大会があって、そこで優勝したら、大型コラボですって！
[Producer: "There's an all-new-song audition, and if you win, it's a massive collab!"]
[プロデューサー] 今すぐ曲準備します！
[Producer: "I'll prepare the song right away!"]
[プロデューサー] ダンスレッスンいれますね！
[Producer: "I'll schedule dance lessons!"]
今から新曲？ダンスレッスン？
A new song starting now? Dance lessons?
ま、間に合うのそれ？
W-Will that even make it in time?
もうライブまでちょっとしかないよ？
There's barely any time left until the concert!
[プロデューサー] 間に合わせてください！もしオーディションに合格したら大型コラボなんですよ！！
[Producer: "Please make it in time! If you pass the audition, it's a massive collab!!"]
えー！！吾輩もう疲れたんですけど！！！！！
Eeh?! But I'm already exhausted!!!!!
大型コラボってなんなの！？
What's this massive collab anyway?!
[プロデューサー] それはまだ、秘密です。
[Producer: "That is still a secret."]
なんでだよおおお！！！！
Why-y-y?!!!!
はぁ…はぁ…はぁ…はぁ…
*pant* *pant* *pant* *pant*
体力ないって言ってるのに…
I told you I have no stamina...
走り込み…？
distance running...?
[プロデューサー] だからこその走り込みです！
[Producer: "That's precisely why you must run!"]
この筋トレ、本当に意味あるの？
Does this muscle training really have any point?!
だあっ…はぁ…あぁぁ…
Gah... haah... aah...
[プロデューサー] よし！良い感じだ！
[Producer: "Nice! Looking good!"]
[プロデューサー] ラプラスさん！本番前に行きましょう！あの方の元へ！
[Producer: "Laplus-san! Let's go before the show! To that person!"]
あ、あの方！？
T-That person?!
あ〜よし！行こう！！
Ah, alright! Let's go!!
ちょこ先生〜〜〜！
Choco-sensei~~~!
あら、いらっしゃい、ラプちゃん。
Oh my, welcome, Lap-chan.
どれにするの？
Which one are you choosing?
う〜ん…
Hmm...
悩んじゃうよね〜。
It's tough to choose, isn't it?
あ〜〜〜
Ahhh~
うん、わかる、わかる〜。
Yeah, I know, I know~
答えは１つじゃないからね〜。
There isn't just one answer, after all~
ラプちゃん、真剣に考えたのね〜。
Lap-chan, you really thought about this seriously, huh~
全部ちゃんと見たいの！
I want to look at all of them properly!
じゃあ、皆さんお待ちかねのグッズ情報よ。
Well then, here is the merchandise information everyone's been waiting for.
ラプちゃ〜ん。
Lap-cha~n!
はーい！
Yes!
はい、はい、はーい！
Yes, yes, yes!
ラプラス・ダークネス誕生日記念2026グッズ！
Laplus Darkness Birthday Celebration 2026 Merchandise!
順番に紹介していきます！
I'll introduce them in order!
じゃん！まずはこちら、カードアルバム！
Ta-da! First up is this: the Card Album!
特典のあのチェキ風ブロマイドカードとか、
The bonus cheki-style bromide cards,
ホロカとかを収納できるアルバムです！
or HoloCards, you can store them in this album!
えっと、めっちゃ久しぶりにくろ…先生が…
Um, for the first time in a while, Kuro...-sensei...
えっと、吾輩のママね！くろねママが、
Um, my Mama! Kurone Mama,
え、描き下ろしてくれました、イラスト！
has drawn a brand-new illustration for this!
イエ〜イ！
Yay!
めっちゃかわいい〜！
It's so cute~!
可愛いでしょ〜！
Cute, right?!
いや、このアルバムぎゅってしてるのがまたいいね。
Hugging the album tight like this is so nice too.
そうでしょ！
Right?!
これもちゃんと、あのアルバムをぎゅっと、
In the illustration, I'm hugging that album,
してるんですよ〜。
tightly holding it~
売ってるやつを！
The very one on sale!
うん。
Yeah.
じゃあ、これ買ったら、ラプちゃんがぎゅっとしたアルバムが手に入るってこと？
So if you buy this, you get the album Lap-chan hugged?
え？
Huh?
それはあの、商品情…
That's, um, product infor...
景表法に問題があります！
That violates misleading advertising laws!
二つ目はこちら！
The second item is this!
興奮ボイスキーホルダー！
Excited Voice Keychain!
え、毎回お馴染みの録り下ろしボイスが、
Loaded with the familiar, newly recorded voices,
6種類入ったキーホルダーです！
it's a keychain featuring 6 different voice lines!
え、押すと声が出ます。いつも通り。
When you press it, a voice plays. As usual.
今回も白子先生の描き下ろしです！
This is also a new illustration by Shiroko-sensei!
メロメロな表情をした、
With an infatuated expression,
オリジナルの雌立ち姿です！
this is my original girly standing pose!
押すと声が出る。
It makes a sound when pressed.
はい。
Yes.
へぇ〜〜〜〜
Heh~~~~
へぇ〜
Heh~
どこを押したらいいのかな〜？
I wonder where I should press~?
え、ど…
Uh, wha...
みっつ…三つ目はこちら！
Th-The third... The third item is this!
え、ばぶラプラスぬいぐるみです！
Um, it's the Baby Laplus Plushie!
えっと、おしゃぶりを…おしゃぶりをくわえて、
Um, sucking on a... sucking on a pacifier,
え、ベイビーウェアを着て寝ている、吾輩のぬいぐるみでございます！
wearing babywear while sleeping, it's a plushie of me!
え、めっちゃかわいい〜！
Woah, it's super cute~!
チョコもぎゅーってしたい！
Choco wants to hug it tight too!
ちょこ先生、そんな…
Choco-sensei, don't say that...
ぎゅーってしたいわぁ。
I really wanna hug you tight.
いつでも…いつでも…
Anytime... anytime...
ああ〜〜
Aah~~
ああ〜〜！
Aah~~!
医療事故だ！やめてください！
That's medical malpractice! Please stop!
本当に…もうまずい、まずい。
Seriously... This is bad, this is bad.
四つ目はこちら！
The fourth item is this!
あ、そうそう、当たっちゃった。
Ah right, it touched.
え、ばぶラプラスぬいぐるみを包める、
Um, you can wrap the Baby Laplus Plushie,
ハンカチです！
in this Handkerchief!
さっきのぬいぐるみをね、包めて、
You can wrap the earlier plushie in it,
あとは普通にハンカチとしても使えます！
and you can also use it normally as a handkerchief!
あ、じゃあおくるみとして使えるってことね？
Ah, so it can be used as a swaddle blanket, right?
そうです！
That's right!
かわいい〜。
Cute~.
でかいっすね、多分。これくらいしかないですよ。
It's pretty big, probably. It's about this size.
これくらい？へぇ〜。
This size? Woah~.
そして最後に、フルセット購入特典として、
And finally, as a Full Set Purchase Bonus,
え、三嶋くろねママ描き下ろしの、
um, newly drawn by Mishima Kurone Mama,
チェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
a cheki-style bromide card comes included!
はい、そして数量限定バージョンは、
Yes, and for the Limited Quantity Version,
はい、書きます！サインを。
yes, I'll write it! My autograph.
直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ってます！
It has a hand-signed autograph and foil-stamped printed message!
通常バージョンは
The standard version includes
箔押しの複製サインとメッセージが入ってるよー
a foil-stamped replica autograph and message!
この配信のあとに販売開始だから、
Sales start right after this stream,
みんな、よろしくねー！
so please check it out, everyone!
お願いしまーす
Please check it out~
以上、グッズ紹介なんですけど、
And that concludes the merch introduction, but...
ちょこ先生、ありがとうございます！
Choco-sensei, thank you so much!
えー、こちらこそー！
Aw, thank you too!
ありがとうございます！これからはちょっとオーディションなんで、新曲の。
Thank you! Up next is the audition for my new song,
おっ！頑張ってね！
Ooh! Good luck!
応援してるね、ラプちゃん！頑張って！
I'll be rooting for you, Lap-chan! Give it your all!
頑張ります！ありがとうー！
I will! Thank youuu!
頑張れー！
Good luck~!
あー！
Ah!
あっ、お姉さまー！あの、今日ライブなのに吾輩、お風呂入ってないんですけど、
Ah, Onee-sama! Even though it's live concert day, I haven't taken a bath yet,
お願いがあって…えへへ。
but I have a favor to ask... Ehehe.
あの、耳舐めてほしいですー！
Um, I want you to lick my ear!
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
すーはー すーはー お姉さま♡
Deep breath in, deep breath out, Onee-sama♡
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
お・ね・え・さ・ま〜〜〜〜！
O-nee-sa-maaaaa!
世の中のお姉さまに捧ぐ
Dedicated to all the older sisters of the world.
あ、お姉さま♡ ああお姉さま♡
Ah, Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
起きたら耳元で囁いて
Whisper in my ear when I wake up,
すーはーお姉さま♡ すーはーお姉さま♡
Inhale Onee-sama♡ Inhale Onee-sama♡
胸元に滴るその汗を
That sweat dripping down your collarbone...
吾輩のお紅茶に入れてゴックンゴックンしたいィww
I want to drip it into my tea and gulp it down! lol
ツノ つの ツノ 掴んでちょうだい
Grab my horns, horns, horns, please!
ハンドル代わりに ほっほっほー！
Use them as handlebars! Ho, ho, ho!
あっ、はっ！お姉さまと視聴者の皆、こんな歌ライブで歌ってごめんなさーい！
Ah, ha! Onee-samas and viewers, I'm so sorry for singing this kind of song live!
あっ、お仕置き！お仕置きしてください！尻尾から手突っ込んで、ガタガタ言わせてください！ツノを！
Ah, punish me! Please punish me! Stick your hand in from my tail and rattle my horns!
あっ、お姉さま今日見入っちゃった…盛り上がってきましたね！
Ah, Onee-sama, I got captivated today... We're really hyping up, aren't we!
えっ？お姉さま！お姉さまちゃん！あっ、お姉さま！あぁ、お世話になっておりますーーー！
Huh? Onee-sama! Onee-sama-chan! Ah, Onee-sama! Thank you for always taking care of meee!
ありがたや ありがたや 「おいで」って言って お姉さま
Grateful, so grateful! Tell me "Come here," Onee-sama!
「雑魚♡ 雑魚♡」言ってください 残さず飲み込むぞ
Please call me "Weakling♡ weakling♡," I'll swallow it all down!
愛のムチ ムチ ムチ ほれ 「お願いなぶって お姉さま」
Love's whip, whip, whip! Here, "Please tease me, Onee-sama!"
キモくてごめんなさい ありのままで キャストオフ！
Sorry for being so creepy! Just as I am, Cast Off!
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
すーはー すーはー お姉さま♡
Deep breath in, deep breath out, Onee-sama♡
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
お・ね・え・さ・ま〜〜〜〜！
O-nee-sa-maaaaa!
刮目せよ！YMDはもう古い！時代はYSOだ！
Behold! YMD is outdated! The new era is YSO!
YSOとは何か？
What does YSO stand for?
そう！「やたらセクシーなお姉さま」だ！
That's right! "Yatara Sexy Onee-sama" (Insanely Sexy Older Sisters)!
YSO! YSO! YSO! YSO!
YSO! YSO!
YSO!!!!!
YY YY YY YSO
お姉さま！お姉さま！
Onee-sama! Onee-sama!
やたらセクシーなお姉さま！
Insanely sexy older sisters!
ほんわか ドジっ子 姉御肌
Gentle, clumsy, big sisterly types,
クーデレ ツンデレ 小悪魔系
Kuudere, tsundere, little devilish types...
色んな姉がいるけれど
There are so many kinds of big sisters,
「あらあらウフフ」が優勝ですw
but the "Ara ara, ufufu" type takes the crown! lol
もち肌！ (ぷにぷに)
Soft skin! (Squish, squish)
太もも？ (すりすり)
Thighs? (Rub, rub)
ギューして！ (ギューして！)
Hug me tight! (Hug me tight!)
居なけりゃ？ (無理無理イイイ)
Without them? (Impossibleeee!)
あぁん、お姉さまがいない世界なんて
Aahn, a world without big sisters...
耐えられないでちゅうううう！！！
is unbearable to meeeeee!!!
そうして、吾輩は、赤ちゃんになった。
And so, I turned into a baby.
なでなで、よしよしされる世界。幸せな世界。
A world of being patted and pampered. A blissful world.
今日もまた、お姉さまの太ももに顔をうずめ、
Today once again, burying my face in Onee-sama's thighs,
涎を垂らす。
drooling away.
これが、人生なのだ。
This is what life is all about.
キモく 正しく 美しく 「おいで」って言って お姉さま
Creepily, righteously, beautifully! Tell me "Come here," Onee-sama!
「抱っこ 抱っこ」してください 本能が剥き出しゾ
Please "Hold me, hold me," my instincts are laid bare!
脚のムチ ムチ ムチ 胸のムチ 「失礼します お姉さま」
Plump thighs, squish, squish, plump chest! "Excuse me, Onee-sama!"
全裸でごめんなさい ありのままで キャストオフ！
Sorry for being naked! Just as I am, Cast Off!
愛してます お姉さま♡
I love you, Onee-sama♡
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
すーはー すーはー お姉さま♡
Deep breath in, deep breath out, Onee-sama♡
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
やたらセクシーなお姉さま♡
Insanely sexy Onee-sama♡
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
すーはー すーはー お姉さま♡
Deep breath in, deep breath out, Onee-sama♡
お姉さま♡ ああ お姉さま♡
Onee-sama♡ Ah, Onee-sama♡
お・ね・え・さ・ま〜〜〜〜！
O-nee-sa-maaaaa!
ば…ばぶぅ…
Ba... Babuu...
ということで
And so,
新曲を
I just performed...
披露させていただきました！
...my brand-new song!
タイトルは
The title is...
「お姉さま
"Big Sis...
お姉さま♡ラヴコール」です！
...Big Sis♡ Love Call"!
ちゃんとお姉さまの後にハートがつくやつです。
It's the one with a heart right after "Big Sis."
え、ビートまりおさんとまろんさんに作ってもらいました。
Um, it was written for me by Beat Mario-san and Maron-san.
依頼した時は、なんか…
When I placed the request, they said...
「最近のラプラスさんを見てたら、なんか楽しく作れました」みたいな言ってくれました。
"Watching recent Laplus-san made it so fun to compose!"
とんでもない曲になっちゃったぜ、へへへ。
It turned into an utterly wild song, hehehe.
収録の時も…
During the recording too...
あ、これはまあ後でリリースされるんですけど、まあなんかね、収録する時もね、
Ah, well, it'll be released later, but during recording...
「なんかもっとキモく！もっと内なるお姉さまへの思いを込めながら歌ってください！」とか言われて。
they told me, "Sing it even creepier! Put more of your inner love for Big Sis into it!"
あんなディレクションは初めてでした。
That was the first time I ever got direction like that.
そんな曲が、このあと、えー、MVがね、私のこのチャンネルでプレミア公開されますよー！
And right after this, the music video for that song will premiere on my channel!
え、そして、まあ今日25日なんですけれど、明日26日に日付変わった瞬間に、
And also, today's the 25th, but the moment the date changes to the 26th tomorrow...
こちらの楽曲がリリースされてしまいます！
...this track will be officially released!
さらに！なんと！
And what's more! Guess what!
まあこれはね、ちょっとサムネにもね、ちょっと釣りみたいな感じでね、「重大告知」みたいな感じで書いたんですけれど、
Well, on the thumbnail, I kinda baited you with "Major Announcement," but...
なんと！ついに！
Amazingly! At long last!
私、ラプラス・ダークネス、
I, Laplus Darknesss...
1人で初めてのアルバムが発売されるぜーーー！イェーーイ！
...am releasing my very first solo album! Yay!
いやあ、なんか1年に1曲しかオリジナル曲出さなかったのに、
Man, even though I used to only release one original song a year...
去年狂ったようにオリ曲出して、今年も出して、
last year I dropped original songs like crazy, and this year too...
アルバムが出せるようになるなんてね、感慨深いでございます。
So being able to release an album feels deeply emotional.
そして、なんと今回は2種類出るんだけど、
And surprisingly, there will be two versions released this time.
え、1つ目がね、ラプラス・ダークネス 1st Album 『ラプ様アーティスト化計画』 高いやつ！
The first one is Laplus Darknesss 1st Album "Lap-sama Artistification Project" - The Expensive One!
ということで、高いやつです。
So yes, the expensive one.
でもう1つが、『ラプ様アーティスト化計画』 安いやつ！
And the other one is "Lap-sama Artistification Project" - The Cheap One!
ということで、えーと、まあちょっとお金を持っている…
So, um, for those who have a bit of money...
ね、大きいお友達用のアルバムと、
...this album is for the older fans,
まあ、お金、ちょ、ママにお願いしようかな。「ママ、買ってー！」みたいなのでお願いできそうな値段の、
and at a price where you could ask, "Mommy, buy it for me!"...
まあ、ホロライブで出てるアルバムだと一番安いんじゃない？っていうぐらい安いやつ、
...the cheap one is cheap enough that it might be the most affordable album in hololive!
の2種類があるよ！
There are those two versions!
え、この配信の後から、ホロライブ公式ショップで予約開始だから、みんな予約してねー！
Pre-orders start on the hololive Official Shop right after this stream, so everyone, go pre-order!
詳しくはホームページをチェック！
Check the official website for details!
さっき披露した新曲も、もちろんアルバムに入るぜ！
The new song I just performed will of course be in the album too!
さ、新曲オーディション終わったしさ、
Well, now that the new song audition is over...
なんかあとは結果待つだけなんで、
...all that's left is to wait for the results,
じゃ、みんなバイバーイ。
so bye-bye, everyone!
お疲れ。
Good work.
なんか優勝したらね、ご褒美って言ってたんだっけな？
Did they say there'd be a reward if I won?
何だろうなー。
I wonder what it is...
プロデューサー: やりましたね！優勝ですよ！
Producer: You did it! You won!
ラプラス・ダークネス: 流石にレッスンとか急すぎたって〜
Laplus Darknesss: The lessons and stuff were way too rushed~
ラプラス・ダークネス: もうへとへと…
Laplus Darknesss: I'm completely exhausted...
プロデューサー: Prrrr
Producer: *Ring ring*
プロデューサー: …はい、分かりました！
Producer: ...Yes, understood!
プロデューサー: ラプラスさん…
Producer: Laplus-san...
ラプラス・ダークネス: お？
Laplus Darknesss: Huh?
プロデューサー: 今すぐいきますよ！！！大型コラボの現場へ！！！
Producer: We're heading out right now! To a massive collab set!
ラプラス・ダークネス: え？なに？え、なに？なに？どこ行くのー？？？
Laplus Darknesss: Huh? What? Huh, what? What? Where are we going?!
みんなーー！こんばんはーーー！
Everyone! Good evening!
来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming!
短い時間だけど、一緒に楽しもうね！
It's only a short time, but let's have fun together!
今日は特別なゲストが来てくれています！
Today we have a special guest with us!
ホロライブのラプラス・ダークネスさんです！
From hololive, it's Laplus Darknesss-san!
えへへへへ。
Ehehehe.
え、莉波... 莉波さん...
Um, Rinami... Rinami-san...
え、あ、ほんとに...
Uh, ah, really...
あ、ほんとに、え、降りてきた本物の... 本物の莉波さんですか？
Ah, really... Is it the real Rinami-san who came down?
はい！初めまして！
Yes! Nice to meet you!
あ、初めまして...
Ah, nice to meet you...
今日はご一緒できて光栄です！
It's an honor to be here with you today!
あ、はい...
Ah, yes...
なんて呼んだらいいですか？
What should I call you?
あ、いや、もう敬語、あの、敬語やめてください。あの...
Ah, no, please drop the polite speech. Um...
我輩のことは、あの、ラ、ラプくんって呼んでください。あの...
Please call me, um, Lap-kun. And, um...
我輩も... 莉、莉波お姉さんって呼んでもい、いいですか？
Can I call you... Rinami-oneesan, too?
もちろん！
Of course!
「莉波お姉さん」って呼んでくれると嬉しいな。
I'd be so happy if you call me "Rinami-oneesan."
ラプくん。
Lap-kun.
ちょっと... 莉波お姉さん...
Wait... Rinami-oneesan...
はい。
Yes.
ラプくん。
Lap-kun.
はい。
Yes.
今日は私の曲を披露させてもらうんだけど、
I get to perform my song today,
ラプくんも会場を盛り上げるために、
and to hype up the venue,
ちょっとだけ一緒に参加してくれるんだよね？
you'll join in with me for a bit, right?
はい、あの、恐縮です。あの、
Yes, um, I'm humbled. Um,
本当はちょっとこんな近くであの、見れるだけでも嬉しいんですけど、
honestly, just being able to watch this close makes me happy, but...
微力ながら参加させていただきます！
I'll do my best to contribute!
うん！
Yeah!
一緒に共演できて嬉しいよ。
I'm so glad we can perform together.
素敵なライブになるといいね。
I hope it turns out to be a wonderful show.
はい！
Yes!
それじゃあ、
Well then,
早速1曲披露させてもらおうかな？
shall I perform a song right away?
ラプくん、
Lap-kun,
準備はいい？
are you ready?
はい、もちろんです！あの、行きます！準備します！行きます！
Yes, of course! Um, I'm going! I'll get ready! Here I go!
みんなも一緒に楽しもうね！
Let's all have fun together!
それでは1曲目、
And now, for the first song,
聴いてください。
please listen.
I know I know border
I know, I know the border
今日は少しだけ
Just for today,
飛び越えてみちゃおっか
shall we try hopping right over it?
全然始まんない
It feels just like watching
物語を見ているような気分
a story that never even starts.
そんな君にお知らせします
I have an announcement for someone like you:
このままいけば
if things go on like this,
エンドロールでいう「エキストラA」
you'll just be "Extra A" in the end credits.
すぐそこのその目の前で手の届く距離にいるのに
I'm right here in front of your eyes, well within reach,
私の目を見て？
so look into my eyes, okay?
冷たい手 ちょっとおでこ貸して？ クラッときちゃった？
Cold hands... Lend me your forehead? Did you get dizzy?
急にギュって キュンもピュアも 私の急を受け取ってよ
Squeezing tight all of a sudden—take my sudden flutter and pure love!
超えてく展開 見てみたいの
I want to see the plot cross the line.
私からのモーションじゃ 大袈裟すぎるでしょ？
If I make the move, it'd be way too obvious, right?
36℃ 初な君に Caution
36℃, a caution to the innocent you!
もうちょい私にお熱をあげてほしいのです
I want you to get just a little more crazy about me.
君にとって 私は一体
To you, just what kind of hurdle
何段のハードル？
am I, anyway?
はい、どうぞ！ ここからは君の番
Go ahead! It's your turn from here on.
上手く言おうとなんてしないで
Don't try too hard to say it smoothly;
ちょっと不自然くらいじゃなきゃ
unless it's a little clumsy,
恋なんてそう 始まりようがないもの
there's no way love can ever begin.
年中平熱な君だけど
You're always at normal temperature,
ちょっとハイなアップルに 浮かされてみない？
but won't you let yourself get swept up by this hyped-up apple?
基本のキ ほんの気のサンバ チャチャチャ
The absolute basics, a samba of mere whims, cha-cha-cha!
挑戦してチャレンジ 世のメンズ達
Step up and take the challenge, men of the world!
ターゲットにタッチ
Touch the target!
放映とすればすべてがチュー
If we broadcast it, everything's a kiss.
もういっちょ love you!
One more time, love you!
頭で考えずに
Without thinking with your head,
脊髄反射で答えて
answer on pure reflex!
当落？ 登場？ どーでもいいよ そうよ
Pass or fail? Making an entrance? Doesn't matter, that's right!
あとちょっと
Just a little more,
もう一歩
one more step!
3, 2, 1で ハイ！
Three, two, one, yes!
やればできる子 素直でよろしい！
You can do it when you try—good job being honest!
36℃ 鈍い君に Caution
36℃, a caution to the oblivious you!
どうせ隠してても ても足も出なくてCD
Even if you hide it, you're helpless—CD!
本音出して
Show your true feelings,
異次元的 素敵をいっぱい感じて
and feel tons of other-dimensional wonder!
はい、どうぞ！ ここからは君の番
Go ahead! It's your turn from here on.
誓う歌も 何て構えないで
Even with a song of vows, don't tense up!
ちょっとくらいの恥じらいがなきゃ
Without at least a little bit of shyness,
恋なんてそう 始まりようがないもの
there's no way love can ever begin.
ラプくん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Lap-kun, happy birthday!
あ、ありがとうございます！
Th-Thank you so much!
一緒に！クラップ！
Together! Clap!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
冷たい手 ちょっとおでこ貸して？ クラッときちゃった？
Cold hands... Lend me your forehead? Did you get dizzy?
急にギュって キュンもピュアも 私の急を受け取ったよ！
Squeezing tight all of a sudden—you took my sudden flutter and pure love!
やっぱ耳朶 茹で卵みたいの
Your earlobes really do look like boiled eggs.
私からのモーションじゃ 大袈裟すぎるでしょ？
If I make the move, it'd be way too obvious, right?
36℃ U・B・Uな君に
To you, who are 36℃ and naive,
テンションもうちょい私にお熱を上げてほしいのです
I want you to raise your enthusiasm and fall for me a little more.
余裕に見えて私もいっぱい いっぱいで
Even if I look composed, I'm already at my limit,
はい 少々本音を打ち明けちゃった
yes, I ended up letting out a bit of my true feelings.
完璧なお姉さんだって
Even as a perfect big sis,
ちょっとくらいの隙じゃなくちゃ好きになって頼れるはずがないもの、でしょ？
if I don't show a little vulnerability, there's no way you'd fall for me and rely on me, right?
だから君を隙だらけで待っています
That's why I'm waiting for you, full of openings,
いつだって
always.
ちょっとハイな熱い波に連れ去られてみたい
I want to be swept away by a passionate, slightly high-spirited wave.
『36℃ U・B・U』でした！
That was "36℃ U・B・U"!
どうだったかなー？
How was it?
最高でしたー！
It was the best!
ラプくん、ありがとー。
Lap-kun, thank you!
一緒にパフォーマンスしてくれて嬉しいよ。
I'm so happy you performed with me.
は、あの、黒子で楽しかったです！
Ah, um, it was so fun being your stagehand!
あの、間近で莉波さんのパフォーマンス見れて、もう、もう光栄でした！
Um, being able to see your performance up close, Rinami-san, it was... such an honor!
ありがとー。
Thank you.
えっと、今日は次の曲が最後になるんだけど…
Um, today the next song will be the last one, but...
えー！早すぎます！まだ見たいです！
Eeh! That's too fast! I still want to see more!
名残惜しいけど、
It's hard to part, but...
次の曲はみんなにも声を出してほしいな。
for the next song, I'd like everyone to cheer along too.
一緒に最後まで楽しもうね！
Let's enjoy it together until the very end!
ラプくんも？
You too, Lap-kun?
もちろんです！もう声枯れるまでやります！
Of course! I'll do it until my voice runs dry!
ラプくん、喉は大事にしてね。
Lap-kun, take care of your throat, okay?
あ、莉波お姉さん、
Ah, Rinami-oneesan,
あの、我輩の先輩もどうしてもライブ見たいって言ってるんですけど、呼んでいいですか？
um, my senpai also really wants to see the concert... can I call her out?
え？誰誰？ぜひ！
Eh? Who is it? By all means!
すみません、まいど、失礼しまーす。
Excuse me, hello, pardon me~
よ、よろしくお願いします！
N-Nice to meet you!
先輩、ありがとう！
Senpai, thank you!
お願いしまーす。
Please have me~
さくらみこさん、お会いできて光栄です。
Sakura Miko-san, it's an honor to meet you.
こ、こちらこそです！パフォーマンス楽しみにしてまーす！
T-The pleasure is all mine! I'm really looking forward to your performance!
お姉さん、頑張っちゃうよ！
Big sis is going to give it her all!
かわ、可愛すぎる…
So, so cute...
それでは、次の曲、聴いてください！
Well then, please listen to the next song!
はみ出したい！
I want to break out!
大層中身作り お茶いかが？ 冷静に「大人」って
Putting on a grand act, "How about some tea?" Calmly playing the "adult,"
ハートは君モード 教えずに ご相談 チラチラチラ
my heart is in "you mode"—without telling you, I ask for advice, glancing, glancing, glancing.
余裕身につけて You お相手は You
Acting composed—You, my partner is You,
ドラマのような事しない女優
an actress who won't do dramatic things.
噛めば噛むほど Delicious
The more you chew, the more delicious it gets.
レディ 玲瓏な甘えた姿を見せてほしい
Lady, I want to show you my clear, pampered side.
一緒に歌ってくれる？
Will you sing along with me?
はーい！
Yes!
はみ出したい！ 囚われないの
I want to break out! (I won't be trapped)
自由型の言う事は好き放題
Speaking freely as a free spirit,
その按配 もう！ 囚われないの
that balance, geez! (I won't be trapped)
優しいフリしてただ焦ってる？
Pretending to be kind, am I just getting anxious?
2人ともよくできました！
You two did a great job!
やったー！ / すごかった！
Yay! / That was awesome!
え、ちょっと…？
Wait, what...?
ラプくん？
Lap-kun?
そっと口角あげ 君を品定め品評
Gently lifting the corners of my mouth, appraising and judging you,
そっと心タップ 君を あぁ君を知りたい
softly tapping your heart, I want to know you, ah, know you.
ラストもお願い！
One last time, please!
はみ出したい！ 囚われないの
I want to break out! (I won't be trapped)
自由型の言う事は好き放題
Speaking freely as a free spirit,
その按配 もう！ 囚われないの
that balance, geez! (I won't be trapped)
優しいフリしてただ焦って
Pretending to be kind, just getting anxious,
もっと！
more!
限界のないワルツをねリードしたいけど
I want to lead a limitless waltz, but
そのボーダーを越えらんないの
I can't cross that border.
そもそもの話 まだ隠して 見つめてる
To begin with, I'm still hiding it, gazing at you.
はいっ
Phew!
clumsy trickでしたー！
That was "clumsy trick"!
どうだったかな？
How did you like it?
最高だったー！／最高です！
It was the best! / It was awesome!
ラプくんとあんな風に一緒にパフォーマンスすることになるなんて…
To think I'd get to perform together with Lap-kun like that...
楽しかったな～
it was so much fun!
よかったら、こっちで一緒に話そうよ！
If you'd like, come up here and talk with me!
えっ？
Eh?!
え、行ってこいよ！
Hey, go on over!
いやいやいや、あの、ここが、ここがやっぱり落ち着くんですけど…
No, no, no... um, I really feel more at ease right here, though...
さっきは一緒にステージにいてくれたのに？
Even though you were on stage with me just a moment ago?
確かに！
She's right!
行ってこいよ！呼ばれてんだから！
Go on! She's inviting you!
え、今行きます！待っててください！
Ah, I'm coming right now! Please wait!
行ってこい！
Go get 'em!
急に出てくるからびっくりしちゃったよ
You showed up so suddenly, you really surprised me!
申し訳ありません、なんか…もう我慢できなくて！
I'm so sorry, I just... couldn't hold back anymore!
そんな破天荒なところがラプくんの魅力だよね
That wild side of yours is part of your charm, Lap-kun!
私も見習いたいよ
I want to learn from you!
え、いや、もう、リリィお姉さんはもうこのままで素敵です！もうそのままでいてください！
Eh, no, Riri-oneesan is already wonderful just the way you are! Please stay just as you are!
ふふっ、ありがとう
Fufu, thank you.
これからもお互いアイドルとして頑張ろうね
Let's keep doing our best as idols together from now on!
あ、恐縮です！もうありがとうございます！頑張ります！
Ah, you're too kind! Thank you so much! I'll do my best!
うん！またこうやって一緒に共演できたら嬉しいな
Yeah! I'd love to perform together again like this sometime!
あ、それ、もう…もう恐れ多すぎます！ありがとうございます！
Ah, th-that's... that's too much of an honor! Thank you so much!
今日はありがとう！
Thank you for today!
とっても素敵なミニライブでした！
It was a truly wonderful mini-live!
みんなも楽しんでくれたかな～？
I hope all of you had a great time too!
それじゃあ、またね！
Well then, see you next time!
ラプくんも！
You too, Lap-kun!
リリィお姉さん…
Riri-oneesan...
お姉さーん…
Oneesaaan...